Guide to the University of Chicago Office of the President, Kimpton Administration Records 1892-1960
University of Chicago Library
- Series I: General Files
  - Telluride Association, Lawrence A. Kimpton, Deep Springs College, 1947-1960 (Box 245, Folder 11-12)
  - Tenure, 1940-1958 (Box 246, Folder 1-2)
  - Tenure, committee on limitation of number, 1951-1952 (Box 246, Folder 3)
  - Tenure policies, 1952-1959 (Box 246, Folder 4)
  - Tenure, Subcommittee on Appointments and Promotions to, 1959 (Box 246, Folder 5)
  - Texas, University of, 1955-1960 (Box 246, Folder 6-8)
  - Theoretical Biology, Department of, Committee on Mathematical Biology, 1945-1958 (Box 246, Folder 9)
  - Theoretical Biology, Department of, Committee on Mathematical Biology, Committee on Space, 1947-1958 (Box 246, Folder 10)
  - Thomas, Hiram W., Lecture Fund Committee, 1938-1959 (Box 246, Folder 11)
  - Time schedules, 1956-1960 (Box 246, Folder 12)
  - "A Traffic Plan for the Hyde Park-Kenwood Area," by George W. Barton and Associates, 1955 (Box 246, Folder 13)
  - Traffic in the university area, 1946-1960 (Box 246, Folder 14-15)
  - Traffic in the university area, vacation of Drexel Avenue between 58th and 59th Streets, 1954-1959 (Box 246, Folder 16)
  - Transportation of staff and students, air travel, 1956-1959 (Box 246, Folder 17)
  - Transportation of staff and students, bus service, 1954-1960 (Box 247, Folder 1-2)
  - Travel expenses, regulations concerning, 1955-1960 (Box 247, Folder 3)
  - Treasurer of the University, Office of, 1953-1959 (Box 247, Folder 4)
  - Treasurer's Office, 1951-1960 (Box 247, Folder 5-6)
  - Trustee-Faculty Dinner, 1952-1954 (Box 247, Folder 7)
  - Trustee-Faculty Dinner, 1955-1960 (Box 248, Folder 1-2)
  - Trustee-Faculty Dinner, speeches, 1952-1956 (Box 248, Folder 3)
  - Trustee-Faculty Dinner, speeches, 1957-1960 (Box 249, Folder 1)
  - Trustees, 1953-1959 (Box 249, Folder 2)
  - Trustees, Board of, 1951-1960 (Box 249, Folder 3-5)
  - Trustees, Board of, Bell, Laird, 1951-1952 (Box 249, Folder 6)
  - Trustees, Board of, chairmanship, Glen Alfred Lloyd, 1956-1963 (Box 250, Folder 1)
  - Trustees, Board of, chairmanship, Harold Higgins Swift, 1933-1955 (Box 250, Folder 2)
  - Trustees, Board of, Chancellor's docket, July 1951-November 1953 (Box 250, Folder 3)
  - Trustees, Board of, Committee on Accounting Practices, 1949-1959 (Box 250, Folder 4)
  - Trustees, Board of, Committee on Alumni Relations, 1951-1952 (Box 250, Folder 5)
  - Trustees, Board of, Committee on Alumni Representation on the Board, ad hoc, 1955-1956 (Box 250, Folder 6)
  - Trustees, Board of, Committee on Enrollment, 1956-1960 (Box 250, Folder 7)
  - Trustees, Board of, Committee on the Organization and Function of, 1958-1959 (Box 250, Folder 8)
  - Trustees, Board of, Committee on Television, 1952-1953 (Box 251, Folder 1)
  - Trustees, Board of, Committee on the Stanley R. Pierce Bequest, 1960 (Box 251, Folder 2)
  - Trustees, Board of, Comptroller's docket, 1951-1952 (Box 251, Folder 3-5)
  - Trustees, Board of, general, 1952 (Box 251, Folder 6)
  - Trustees, Board of, Lakeside Planning Conference, I, 1954 (Box 251, Folder 7)
  - Trustees, Board of, Lakeside Planning Conference, I, 1954 (Box 252, Folder 1)
  - Trustees, Board of, Lakeside Planning Conference, II, 1956 (Box 252, Folder 2-4)
  - Trustees, Board of, Lakeside Planning Conference, III, 1956 (Box 252, Folder 5-6)
  - Trustees, Board of, Lakeside Planning Conference, III, 1956 (Box 253, Folder 1)
  - Trustees, Board of, Lakeside Planning Conference, IV, 1957 (Box 253, Folder 2-5)
  - Trustees, Board of, Lakeside Planning Conference, V, 1958 (Box 254, Folder 1-2)
  - Trustees, Board of, Lakeside Planning Conference, VI, 1958 (Box 254, Folder 3)
  - Trustees, Board of, Lakeside Planning Conference, VII, 1958 (Box 254, Folder 4-5)
  - Trustees, Board of, Lakeside Planning Conference, VII, 1958 (Box 255, Folder 1)
  - Trustees, Board of, Lakeside Planning Conference, VIII, 1959 (Box 255, Folder 2-4)
  - Trustees, Board of, Lakeside Planning Conference, IX, 1959 (Box 255, Folder 5)
  - Trustees, Board of, Lakeside Planning Conference X, 1960 (Box 256, Folder 1-3)
  - Trustees, Board of, Lakeside Planning Conference XI, 1960 (Box 256, Folder 4)
  - Trustees, Board of, medical services and charges for trustees, 1951-1960 (Box 257, Folder 1)
  - Trustees, Board of, meetings, 1950-1958 (Box 257, Folder 2-9)
  - Trustees, Board of, meetings, 1959-1960 (Box 258, Folder 1-2)
  - Trustees, Board of, members, Trevor Arnett, 1924-1956 (Box 258, Folder 3)
  - Trustees, Board of, members, Edward Eagle Brown, 1944-1954 (Box 258, Folder 4)
  - Trustees, Board of, members, Laird Bell, 1949-1953 (Box 258, Folder 5)
  - Trustees, Board of, members, Thomas Elliott Donnelley, 1942-1953 (Box 258, Folder 6)
  - Trustees, Board of, members, Max Epstein, 1931-1954 (Box 258, Folder 7)
  - Trustees, Board of, members, Marshall Field, 1920-1957 (Box 258, Folder 8)
  - Trustees, Board of, members, Harry Barnes Gear, 1924-1959 (Box 258, Folder 9)
  - Trustees, Board of, members, Charles W. Gilkey, 1929-1955 (Box 259, Folder 1)
  - Trustees, Board of, members, Howell W. Murray, 1952-1957 (Box 259, Folder 2)
  - Trustees, Board of, members, Edward Larned Ryerson, 1953-1956 (Box 259, Folder 3)
  - Trustees, Board of, members, Robert L. Scott, 1943-1953 (Box 259, Folder 4)
  - Trustees, Board of, members, David Becker Stern, 1945-1960 (Box 259, Folder 5)
  - Trustees, Board of, members, John P. Wilson, 1930-1959 (Box 259, Folder 6)
  - Trustees, Board of, Secretary's docket, 1949-1953 (Box 259, Folder 7-9)
  - Trustees, Board of, Secretary's docket, 1953-1954 (Box 260, Folder 1)
  - Trustees, Board of, Secretary's Office, 1940-1958 (Box 260, Folder 2)
  - Trustees, Board of, Treasurer's docket, July 1946-June 1952 (Box 260, Folder 3)
  - Trustees, Board of, Vice-President in Charge of Business Affairs, dockets, 1950-1952 (Box 260, Folder 4)
  - Trustees, Board of, Vice-President in Charge of Development, 1954-1957 (Box 260, Folder 5-7)
  - Trustees, Board of, Vice-President in Charge of Development, 1957-1958 (Box 261, Folder 1)
  - Trustees, Board of, Vice-President in Charge of Development, Trustees Dinner, 1939-1957 (Box 261, Folder 2)
  - Trustees, Development Committee, 1959 (Box 261, Folder 3)
  - Trustees Fund, 1941-1960 (Box 261, Folder 4)
  - Trustees Fund, expenses, 1959-1960 (Box 261, Folder 5)
  - Trustees, President’s luncheons and dinners, 1953-1960 (Box 261, Folder 6-7)
  - Trustees wives, cocktail parties, luncheons, and dinners, 1954-1960 (Box 261, Folder 8)
  - Trustees wives steering committee, 1954-1958 (Box 262, Folder 1)
  - Tuition Deferment Loans, 1952-1960 (Box 262, Folder 2-3)
  - Tuition deferment and remission, 1954-1959 (Box 262, Folder 4)
  - Tuition Exchange, Committee to Study, 1955-1956 (Box 262, Folder 5)
  - Tuition payments in advance, plan for, 1956-1960 (Box 262, Folder 6)
  - Tuition Plan, Inc., 1955-1960 (Box 262, Folder 7)
  - Tuition remission, laboratory schools, 1952-1959 (Box 262, Folder 8)
  - Tuition remission, teachers and MATS program, 1953-1960 (Box 262, Folder 9)
  - Tulane University, 1958-1960 (Box 262, Folder 10)
  - Unalienable Rights, Incorporated, 1954 (Box 262, Folder 11)
  - Undergraduate Education, Executive Committee on, general, 1949-1958 (Box 262, Folder 12)
  - Undergraduate Education, Executive Committee on, general, 1949-1958 (Box 263, Folder 1)
  - Undergraduate Education, Executive Committee on, establishment and recommendations, November 1956-December 1957 (Box 263, Folder 2-3)
  - Undergraduate Education, Executive Committee on, membership, 1957-1958 (Box 263, Folder 4)
  - Undergraduate Education, Executive Committee on, minutes and agendas, April 1957-May 1958 (Box 263, Folder 5-6)
  - Undergraduate Education, Executive Committee on, recommendations, January 1958-April 1958 (Box 263, Folder 7-8)
  - Undergraduate Library Needs, Committee on, 1955-1956 (Box 263, Folder 9)
  - UNESCO, 1950-1959 (Box 264, Folder 1)
  - Union League Club, 1953-1960 (Box 264, Folder 2)
  - Unions, 1955-1960 (Box 264, Folder 3)
  - Unions, AFL-CIO, union, 1957-1960 (Box 264, Folder 4)
  - Unions, AFSCME, 1952-1953 (Box 264, Folder 5-6)
  - Unions, AFSCME, AFL-CIO, Local 1657, 1955-1958 (Box 264, Folder 7)
  - Unions at the university, American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees, 1955-1960 (Box 264, Folder 8)
  - Unions at the university, American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees, contract negotiations, 1959-1960 (Box 265, Folder 1)
  - Unions at the university, University of Chicago Council, AFL-CIO, 1948-1954 (Box 265, Folder 2)
  - Unions at the university, University of Chicago Council, AFL-CIO, 1955-1959 (Box 265, Folder 3)
  - Unions at the university, University of Chicago Council, AFL-CIO, contract negotiation meeting minutes, 1951-1955 (Box 265, Folder 4)
  - Unions at the university, University of Chicago Employees Union, 1952-1954 (Box 265, Folder 5)
  - Unions, Journeymen Barbers’ Union, Local 548, 1952-1953 (Box 265, Folder 6)
  - Unions, National Labor Relations Board, 1954 (Box 265, Folder 7)
  - Unitarian, 1952-1960 (Box 265, Folder 8)
  - United Charities of Chicago, 1958-1959 (Box 266, Folder 1)
  - United Church of Hyde Park, 1960 (Box 266, Folder 2)
  - United Nations, 1951-1960 (Box 266, Folder 3)
  - United States, 1951-1960 (Box 266, Folder 4-6)
  - United States, Air Force, 1941-1960 (Box 266, Folder 7-9)
  - United States, Air Force Academy, 1955-1956 (Box 266, Folder 10)
  - United States, Air Force Cambridge Research Laboratories, 1950-1957 (Box 266, Folder 11)
  - United States, Armed Forces Industrial College, 1960 (Box 266, Folder 12)
  - United States Atomic Energy Commission, 1959-1960 (Box 267, Folder 1-2)
  - United States Central Intelligence Agency, university involvement, 1952-1960 (Box 267, Folder 3)
  - United States, Committee on National Objectives, 1959-1960 (Box 267, Folder 4-5)
  - United States, Department of Agriculture, 1938-1955 (Box 267, Folder 6)
  - United States Department of Commerce, 1959 (Box 267, Folder 7)
  - United States Department of Defense, 1951-1959 (Box 267, Folder 8)
  - United States Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1953-1960 (Box 267, Folder 9)
  - United States Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, 1957-1960 (Box 268, Folder 1)
  - United States Department of Labor, 1959 (Box 268, Folder 2)
  - United States Department of State, 1954-1960 (Box 268, Folder 3-5)
  - United States Department of State, foreign service, 1956-1959 (Box 268, Folder 6)
  - United States Department of State, Program for the Exchange of Persons, 1951-1953 (Box 268, Folder 7)
  - United States, Foreign Currencies of Education, Agricultural Trade Development and Assistance Act of 1954, and Dingell Amendment, 1958 (Box 268, Folder 8)
  - United States, general, 1951-1960 (Box 268, Folder 9)
  - United States Marine Corps, 1946-1960 (Box 268, Folder 10)
  - United States National Student Association, 1958-1960, Folders12-13: United States Navy, 1945-1960 (Box 268, Folder 11)
  - United States Navy, Home Study, Navy Project, 1960 (Box 269, Folder 1)
  - United States Navy, Office of Naval Research, 1945-1960 (Box 269, Folder 2-3)
  - United States, Office of Education, 1951-1952 (Box 269, Folder 4)
  - United States, Office of Scientific Research and Development, Committee on Aid to Research, 1943-1954 (Box 269, Folder 5)
  - United States, President's Committee on Education Beyond the High School, 1956-1957 (Box 269, Folder 6-7)
  - United States, President's Committee on Scientists and Engineers, 1957-1958 (Box 269, Folder 8)
  - United States, President’s Science Advisor and Advisory Committee, 1960 (Box 269, Folder 9)
  - United States, President's Science Advisory Committee, 1958-1959 (Box 269, Folder 10)
  - United States Public Health Service, 1951-1954 (Box 269, Folder 11)
  - United States Public Health Service, 1955-1959 (Box 270, Folder 1)
  - United States Social Security System, 1951-1960 (Box 270, Folder 2)
  - "Unity and Variety in Muslim Civilization," University of Liege Conference, 1953 (Box 270, Folder 3)
  - Unity Publishing Corporation, 1959-1960 (Box 270, Folder 4)
  - University and World Affairs, Committee on, created by Ford Foundation, 1959 (Box 270, Folder 5)
  - University Architect, Office of, 1957-1960 (Box 270, Folder 6)
  - University awards and prizes, Rosenberger, Jesse, Medal, recipients of, Field, Marshall, III, 1955 (Box 270, Folder 7)
  - University awards and prizes, Rosenberger, Jesse, Medal, recipients of, Hoehler, Fred, Kenneth, 1953 (Box 270, Folder 8)
  - University awards and prizes, Rosenberger, Jesse, Medal, recipients of, Nourse, Edwin Griswold, 1959 (Box 270, Folder 9)
  - University awards and prizes, student, honors awards assemblies, 1957-1960 (Box 270, Folder 10)
  - University band, 1954-1959 (Box 270, Folder 11)
  - University calendar, academic, proposed for 1953-1954 (Box 270, Folder 12)
  - University calendar, appointment, 1955-1958 (Box 270, Folder 13)
  - University calendars, 1955-1959 (Box 270, Folder 14)
  - University of Chicago, General Plan, Report to the Committee on Campus Improvement and Development, 1954 (Box 270, Folder 15)
  - University of Chicago Press, 1951-1953 (Box 270, Folder 16-17)
  - University of Chicago Press, 1954-1960 (Box 271, Folder 1-2)
  - University of Chicago Press, Booz, Allen, and Hamilton surveys, Printing Department, survey of operations, 1949-1952 (Box 271, Folder 3)
  - University of Chicago Press, Committee on, 1951 (Box 271, Folder 4)
  - University of Chicago Press, Directorship, 1951 (Box 271, Folder 5)
  - University of Chicago Press, journals published by the University Press, American Journal of Sociology, 1933-1954 (Box 271, Folder 6)
  - University of Chicago Press, journals published by the University Press, Journal of General Education, 1943-1960 (Box 271, Folder 7)
  - University of Chicago Press, journals published by the University Press, Journal of Geology, 1927-1958 (Box 271, Folder 8)
  - University of Chicago Press, journals published by the University Press, Journal of Infectious Diseases, 1940-1960 (Box 271, Folder 9)
  - University of Chicago Press, journals published by the University Press, Journal of Classical Philology, 1938-1956 (Box 271, Folder 10)
  - University of Chicago Press, journals published by the University Press, Modern Philology, 1952-1956 (Box 271, Folder 11)
  - University of Chicago Press, Printing Department, 1945-1959 (Box 271, Folder 12-13)
  - University of Chicago Press, publications, 1955-1960 (Box 271, Folder 14)
  - University of Chicago Press, space, 1952-1955 (Box 271, Folder 15)
  - University of Chicago Reports, 1950-1954 (Box 271, Folder 16)
  - University of Chicago Round Table, 1951-1958 (Box 271, Folder 17)
  - University of Chicago Round Table, Committee to Study, 1951 (Box 271, Folder 18)
  - University of Chicago Settlement, 1951-1954 (Box 272, Folder 1)
  - University College, 1951-1954 (Box 272, Folder 2-3)
  - University College, 1955-1957 (Box 272, Folder 4-7)
  - University College, "A History of the Origins of Adult Education at the University of Chicago and of Sixty-Two Years at the Downtown Center," by Betty Fackler Heycke, 1959 (Box 272, Folder 8)
  - University College, Basic Problems Self Study Committee, 1958 (Box 272, Folder 9)
  - University College, Basic Problems Self Study Committee, 1958 (Box 273, Folder 1)
  - University College, Basic Program of Liberal Education for Adults, 1946-1959 (Box 273, Folder 2)
  - University College, Center for Programs in Government Administration, 1959-1960 (Box 273, Folder 3)
  - University College, Extension Division, Fine Arts Program, 1958-1960 (Box 273, Folder 4)
  - University College, general, 1928-1960 (Box 273, Folder 5-7)
  - University College, Labor Education Project, 1949-1960 (Box 273, Folder 8-10)
  - University College, Labor Education Project, 1949-1960 (Box 274, Folder 1)
  - University College, Manuscript on University College Students, Student Questionnaire, 1958 (Box 274, Folder 2-3)
  - University College, Program of Executive Development for Federal Administrators, 1957-1960 (Box 274, Folder 4-5)
  - University College, promotional material, 1954-1958 (Box 274, Folder 6-7)
  - University College, reorganization, 1958-1960 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - University College, Self-Study Advisory Committee, 1957-1959 (Box 275, Folder 1)
  - University College, Self Study Advisory Committee Reports, October 1, 1959 (Box 275, Folder 2)
  - University College, Self Study Committee, 1957-1959 (Box 275, Folder 3)
  - University College, Sub-Committee to Make Inquiry into Quality of and Relationship to Faculties, 1959-1960 (Box 275, Folder 4)
  - University Corporation for Atmospheric Research, 1959-1960 (Box 275, Folder 5)
  - University Extension, space, 64 East Lake Street, 1956-1960 (Box 275, Folder 6)
  - University Extension and College, basic program of liberal education for adults, 1953-1959 (Box 275, Folder 7)
  - University health service, faculty and staff, 1954-1956 (Box 275, Folder 8)
  - University health service, student health service, 1950-1960 (Box 275, Folder 9)
  - University High School alumni, active lists, January 1960 (Box 276, Folder 1)
  - University High School alumni, mailing pieces, samples, 1958 (Box 276, Folder 2)
  - University High School alumni, reunion dinner, February 11, 1959 (Box 276, Folder 3)
  - University High School alumni, reunion picnic, June 13, 1959 (Box 276, Folder 4)
  - University of Illinois, Analysis of sites for the campus of the Chicago Undergraduate Division, 1958 (Box 276, Folder 5)
  - University memberships, Wayfarers Club, 1959 (Box 276, Folder 6)
  - University Record, 1928-1958 (Box 276, Folder 7)
  - University Senate, 1952-1960 (Box 276, Folder 8)
  - University Senate, Committee of the Council, 1945-1958 (Box 276, Folder 9-11)
  - University Senate, Committee of the Council, 1955-1960 (Box 277, Folder 1)
  - University Senate, Committee of the Council, Committee on the Bachelor's Degree, 1953 (Box 277, Folder 2)
  - University Senate, Committee of the Council, Committee on the Evaluation of the University, 1957-1958 (Box 277, Folder 3)
  - University Senate, Committee of the Council, Committee/Subcommittee on Enrollment, 1953 (Box 277, Folder 4)
  - University Senate, Committee of the Council, Committee on the Form E Contracts, report, 1952-1953 (Box 277, Folder 5)
  - University Senate, Committee of the Council, Committee on International Exchange, 1952-1953 (Box 277, Folder 6)
  - University Senate, Committee of the Council, Committee/Subcommittee on the Laboratory School, 1950-1952 (Box 277, Folder 7)
  - University Senate, Committee of the Council, elections, 1945-1954 (Box 277, Folder 8-9)
  - University Senate, Committee of the Council, elections and membership, 1951-1960 (Box 277, Folder 10)
  - University Senate, Committee of the Council, summer quarter discussions, 1959-1960 (Box 277, Folder 11)
  - University Senate, Committee of the Council, Committee on the Ph.D. in the Professional School, 1960 (Box 277, Folder 12)
  - University Theatre, 1950-1960 (Box 278, Folder 1-2)
  - Urban renewal, advertising, 1959 (Box 278, Folder 3)
  - Urban renewal, American Association of Universities, study, 1957-1958 (Box 278, Folder 4)
  - Urban renewal, American Council on Education, 1959-1960 (Box 278, Folder 5-6)
  - Urban renewal, American Council to Improve our Neighborhoods, 1956-1958 (Box 278, Folder 7)
  - Urban renewal, "Analysis of Feasibility of Rehabilitation of Residential Structures," report, 1959 (Box 278, Folder 8)
  - Urban renewal, architecture, 1959-1960 (Box 278, Folder 9-10)
  - Urban renewal, Atrium Homes, 1960 (Box 278, Folder 11)
  - Urban renewal, campus security, 1955-1960 (Box 278, Folder 12)
  - Urban renewal, Catholic position, 1958 (Box 278, Folder 13)
  - Urban renewal, Chicago, 1952-1960 (Box 278, Folder 14-18)
  - Urban renewal, city planning, 1959 (Box 278, Folder 19)
  - Urban renewal, comments and editorials, 1954-1958 (Box 279, Folder 1)
  - Urban renewal, Community Conservation Board of Chicago, 1958-1959 (Box 279, Folder 2)
  - Urban renewal, correspondence, 1958-1960 (Box 279, Folder 3)
  - Urban renewal, crime in area, 1960 (Box 279, Folder 4)
  - Urban renewal, crime in Chicago, 1957-1960 (Box 279, Folder 5)
  - Urban renewal, crime, luncheon meeting reports, 1959-1960 (Box 279, Folder 6)
  - Urban renewal, crime, youth problems, 1959 (Box 279, Folder 7-8)
  - Urban renewal, Field Foundation proposal, 1959 (Box 279, Folder 9)
  - Urban renewal, financing, 1956-1959 (Box 279, Folder 10)
  - Urban renewal, Ford Foundation proposals, 1957 (Box 279, Folder 11)
  - Urban renewal, Fulton Morrissey, 1959 (Box 279, Folder 12)
  - Urban renewal, hotels and motels, Chicago, 1959-1960 (Box 279, Folder 13)
  - Urban renewal, housing, 1958-1960 (Box 279, Folder 14)
  - Urban renewal, Hyde Park- Kenwood, 1952-1959 (Box 279, Folder 15-16)
  - Urban renewal, Hyde Park-Kenwood, 1954-1958 (Box 280, Folder 1-6)
  - Urban renewal, Hyde Park-Kenwood, apartments, 1959-1960 (Box 280, Folder 7)
  - Urban renewal, Hyde Park-Kenwood, Chicago Tribune article, 1959 (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - Urban renewal, Hyde Park-Kenwood Community Conference, 1956-1960 (Box 281, Folder 2)
  - Urban renewal, Hyde Park-Kenwood community directory, 1959-1960 (Box 281, Folder 3)
  - Urban renewal, Hyde Park-Kenwood, East Hyde Park, 1956-1958 (Box 281, Folder 4-5)
  - Urban renewal, Hyde Park-Kenwood, Illinois Central Magazine article, 1959 (Box 281, Folder 6)
  - Urban renewal, Hyde Park-Kenwood, New York Times article, 1959 (Box 281, Folder 7)
  - Urban renewal, Hyde Park-Kenwood, projects A and B, 1953-1958 (Box 281, Folder 8-9)
  - Urban renewal, Hyde Park-Kenwood, proposed ordinance, 1958 (Box 281, Folder 10)
  - Urban renewal, Hyde Park-Kenwood, public relations luncheon, 1959 (Box 281, Folder 11)
  - Urban renewal, Hyde Park-Kenwood schools, 1956-1958 (Box 281, Folder 12)
  - Urban renewal, Hyde Park schools, 1958-1960 (Box 281, Folder 13)
  - Urban renewal, Hyde Park transportation, 1959 (Box 281, Folder 14)
  - Urban renewal, index of slides, 1960 (Box 282, Folder 1)
  - Urban renewal, legislation, proposed housing bill, 1958-1959 (Box 282, Folder 2-3)
  - Urban renewal, Leon M. Despres, 1959 (Box 282, Folder 4)
  - Urban renewal, maps, 1960 (Box 282, Folder 5)
  - Urban renewal, neighborhood organizations, 1958-1959 (Box 282, Folder 6)
  - Urban renewal, "New Hyde Park" exhibit, photographs, 1960 (Box 282, Folder 7-8)
  - Urban renewal, promotion, 1955-1959 (Box 282, Folder 9)
  - Urban renewal, race relations, 1958-1959 (Box 282, Folder 10)
  - Urban renewal, renovation of 5409-5411 Blackstone Ave., 1960 (Box 282, Folder 11)
  - Urban renewal, slum clearance and redevelopment programs, 1958-1960 (Box 282, Folder 12)
  - Urban renewal, South East Chicago Commission, 1952-1960 (Box 282, Folder 13-14)
  - Urban renewal, South East Chicago Commission, Julian Levi, speeches, 1958-1960 (Box 283, Folder 1)
  - Urban renewal, South East Chicago Commission, publications, 1952-1957 (Box 283, Folder 2)
  - Urban renewal, Southwest Hyde Park Neighborhood Association, 1956 (Box 283, Folder 3)
  - Urban renewal, Southwest Hyde Park Neighborhood Redevelopment Corporation and South East Chicago Commission, 1956-1959 (Box 283, Folder 4)
  - Urban renewal, Talmanac, 1959 (Box 283, Folder 5)
  - Urban renewal, university public relations, proposal for filming, 1960 (Box 283, Folder 6)
  - Urban renewal, university, new buildings, 1956-1960 (Box 283, Folder 8)
  - Urban renewal, Web and Knapp, 1955-1959 (Box 284, Folder 1)
  - Urban renewal, Woodlawn, news releases, 1954-1959 (Box 284, Folder 2)
  - Uruguay, general, 1959-1960 (Box 284, Folder 3)
  - U.S. Air Force, Air Research and Development Command, 1958-1960 (Box 284, Folder 4)